{
    "subject": "resource/Warner_Baxter",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Warner Leroy Baxter (March 29, 1889 \u2013 May 7, 1951) was an American actor, known for his role as The Cisco Kid in In Old Arizona (1929), for which he won the second Academy Award for Best Actor in the 1928\u20131929 Academy Awards. He frequently played womanizing, charismatic Latin bandit types in westerns, and played The Cisco Kid or a similar character throughout the 1930s, but had a range of other roles throughout his career. Warner Baxter started his movie career in silent film. Baxter's most notable silent films are The Great Gatsby (1926) and The Awful Truth (1925). When talkies came out, Baxter became even more famous. Baxter's most notable talkies are In Old Arizona (1929) 42nd Street (1932), Slave Ship (1937), Kidnapped (1938), and the 1931 20 minute all-star ensemble short film, The Stolen Jools. In the 1940s he was well known for his recurring role as Dr. Robert Ordway in the Crime Doctor series of 10 films.",
    "human_readable": "Warner Baxter's abstract is Warner Leroy Baxter (March 29, 1889 \u2013 May 7, 1951) was an American actor, known for his role as The Cisco Kid in In Old Arizona (1929), for which he won the second Academy Award for Best Actor in the 1928\u20131929 Academy Awards. He frequently played womanizing, charismatic Latin bandit types in westerns, and played The Cisco Kid or a similar character throughout the 1930s, but had a range of other roles throughout his career. Warner Baxter started his movie career in silent film. Baxter's most notable silent films are The Great Gatsby (1926) and The Awful Truth (1925). When talkies came out, Baxter became even more famous. Baxter's most notable talkies are In Old Arizona (1929), 42nd Street (1932), Slave Ship (1937), Kidnapped (1938), and the 1931 20-minute all-star ensemble short film, The Stolen Jools. In the 1940s he was well known for his recurring role as Dr. Robert Ordway in the Crime Doctor series of 10 films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8107680082321167,
            "question": "Name two notable silent films starring Warner Baxter."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7967919111251831,
            "question": "Which film earned Warner Baxter his second Academy Award for Best Actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7531089782714844,
            "question": "What type of characters did Warner Baxter frequently play in westerns?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7196465730667114,
            "question": "How did Warner Baxter's career evolve with the advent of talkies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6966826319694519,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other role might have contributed to Warner Baxter's success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6905688643455505,
            "question": "When did Warner Baxter's career primarily flourish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6895469427108765,
            "question": "What was Warner Baxter best known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5931735634803772,
            "question": "What year was Warner Baxter born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5558174848556519,
            "question": "What was the title of the 20-minute all-star short film featuring Warner Baxter in 1931?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.538350522518158,
            "question": "In which film series did Warner Baxter have a recurring role as Dr. Robert Ordway?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Warner Baxter's abstract is Warner Leroy Baxter (March 29, 1889 \u2013 May 7, 1951) was an American actor, known for his role as The Cisco Kid in In Old Arizona (1929), for which he won the second Academy Award for Best Actor in the 1928\u20131929 Academy Awards. He frequently played womanizing, charismatic Latin bandit types in westerns, and played The Cisco Kid or a similar character throughout the 1930s, but had a range of other roles throughout his career. Warner Baxter started his movie career in silent film. Baxter's most notable silent films are The Great Gatsby (1926) and The Awful Truth (1925). When talkies came out, Baxter became even more famous. Baxter's most notable talkies are In Old Arizona (1929), 42nd Street (1932), Slave Ship (1937), Kidnapped (1938), and the 1931 20-minute all-star ensemble short film, The Stolen Jools. In the 1940s he was well known for his recurring role as Dr. Robert Ordway in the Crime Doctor series of 10 films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7197_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the title of the 20-minute all-star short film featuring Warner Baxter in 1931?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7197_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Warner Baxter born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7197_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Warner Baxter best known for playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7197_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7197_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is actually asking to evaluate whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"Warner Baxter's abstract is Warner Leroy Baxter (March 29, 1889 \u2013 May 7, 1951) was an American actor...\". However, based on your response format, I will assume you are looking for a more general evaluation of the correctness of the statement.\n\nHere is my evaluation:\n\nThe documents indeed mention Warner Baxter's full name as \"Warner Leroy Baxter\" and provide his birth and death dates. They also describe him as an American actor and mention his notable roles in various films, including The Great Gatsby, In Old Arizona, and others.\n\nGiven this information, I believe the triple is correct according to the documents.\n\nHere is my response in the required format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}